{
    "subject": "resource/Sam_Coghlan_Murray",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Australia",
    "human_readable": "Sam Coghlan Murray was born in Australia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9595015048980713,
            "question": "Is Sam Coghlan Murray Australian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9406253695487976,
            "question": "Where was Sam Coghlan Murray born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6875135898590088,
            "question": "What country is Sam Coghlan Murray from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6090882420539856,
            "question": "What is Sam Coghlan Murray known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4881547689437866,
            "question": "What can you infer about Sam Coghlan Murray's upbringing based on his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4528466463088989,
            "question": "Is there any public information available about Sam Coghlan Murray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43911081552505493,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Sam Coghlan Murray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4247809052467346,
            "question": "Where might Sam Coghlan Murray live now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3908337354660034,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Sam Coghlan Murray's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34780749678611755,
            "question": "Does Sam Coghlan Murray have any notable accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sam Coghlan Murray was born in Australia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_333_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about Sam Coghlan Murray's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_333_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Sam Coghlan Murray live now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_333_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Sam Coghlan Murray?",
            "html": "dbpedia_333_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_333_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that Sam Coghlan Murray's place of birth is Brisbane, Queensland, Australia. Therefore, the statement \"Sam Coghlan Murray was born in Australia\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}